=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 7=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 7 =
(Recording)
(تسجيل)
I've got to go, bye.
يجب أن أذهب ، وداعا.
Bye.
وداعا.
Aunt.
عمة.
Liu,
ليو ،
where's your mask?
اين قناعك
Well,
نحن سوف،
there wasn't enough time,
لم يكن هناك ما يكفي من الوقت ،
so I didn't find one.
لذلك لم أجد واحدة.
Where did you buy this bag?
من أين اشتريت هذه الحقيبة؟
Aunt,
عمة،
if you like this bag,
إذا كنت تحب هذه الحقيبة ،
I can give it to you.
أستطيع أن أعطيها لك.
Just take it
خذها و حسب
as a gift from me
كهدية مني
for your birthday.
لعيد ميلادك.
Besides this bag,
بجانب هذه الحقيبة ،
there should be something else, right?
يجب أن يكون هناك شيء آخر ، أليس كذلك؟
What about the shares that we talked about before?
ماذا عن الأسهم التي تحدثنا عنها من قبل؟
Aunt,
عمة،
what's your purpose
ما هو غرضك
in taking my shares?
في أخذ أسهمي؟
Why are you talking like this?
لماذا تتحدث بهذه الطريقة؟
Don't you believe me?
الا تصدقني
What's wrong, Ms. Mu?
ما بك يا سيدة مو؟
You are not happy
انت لست سعيدا
with my fiancee's decision?
بقرار خطيبتي؟
Sorry to bother you, Mr. Mo.
آسف على إزعاجك ، سيد مو.
This is the Mus' family affair,
هذه هي شأن عائلة المصحف.
so you don't need to intervene.
لذلك لا داعي للتدخل.
You'd better take care of yourself.
من الأفضل أن تعتني بنفسك.
You!
أنت!
Aunt,
عمة،
excuse us, we're going over there.
عفوا ، نحن ذاهبون هناك.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Don't think
لا تفكر
that if you spoke up for me,
أنه إذا تحدثت نيابة عني ،
I will forgive you.
سوف اسامحك.
If I didn't come,
إذا لم آتي ،
who would help you out?
من سيساعدك؟
Mr. Mo, you didn't need
السيد مو ، أنت لا تحتاج
to come over here
للمجيء إلى هنا
and help me out.
وساعدني.
Or
أو
did you come to the dance
هل جئت للرقص
for another dirty secret?
لسر قذر آخر؟
No good deed goes unpunished.
لا يمر عمل جيد بلا عقاب.
Go in by yourself.
ادخل بنفسك.
I'll walk around and leave.
سوف أتجول وأرحل.
Hem.
هدب.
Goodbye!
مع السلامة!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Mr. Luo.
السيد لو.
Mr. Mo,
السيد.  مو ،
I heard
سمعت
that Miss Mu wanted to break off the engagement.
أن الآنسة مو أرادت فسخ الخطوبة.
When other shareholders heard the news,
عندما سمع المساهمون الآخرون بالأخبار ،
they were ready to give up working with you.
كانوا على استعداد للتخلي عن العمل معك.
Mr. Luo,
السيد لو ،
I have a good relationship with her.
لدي علاقة جيدة معها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
OK.
نعم.
(He didn't come for me.)
(لم يأت من أجلي.)
Liu,
ليو ،
I'm so happy
انا سعيد للغاية
to see you back safely.
لرؤيتك تعود بأمان.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm Song Yuan.
أنا سونغ يوان.
You have changed
لقد تغيرت
and become more beautiful.
وتصبح أكثر جمالا.
Mr. Luo.
السيد لو.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
(So he is Song Yuan.)
(إذن هو سونغ يوان.)
What?
ماذا؟
It's been a long time,
لقد مر وقت طويل ،
so you forgot about me?
اذا نسيت عني؟
Return my money!
إعادة أموالي!
What money?
ما المال؟
Two million RMB and return it quickly!
مليوني يوان وإعادته بسرعة!
We have
نملك
donated the money as you said,
تبرع بالمال كما قلت ،
haven't we?
أليس كذلك؟
You forgot?
أنت نسيت؟
I...
أنا...
Ah,
آه،
I had an accident
حدث لي حادث
and hit my head.
وضربت رأسي.
I can't remember many things clearly.
لا أستطيع تذكر أشياء كثيرة بوضوح.
Tell me more about it.
أخبرني المزيد عنه.
Come on.
هيا.
Let's
دعونا
drink
يشرب
and recall it.
وأذكرها.
Why are you
لماذا انت
still hanging with such a man?
ما زلت معلقة مع مثل هذا الرجل؟
Whoever I hang with,
مع من أعلق ،
it has nothing to do with you, OK?
لا علاقة لك به ، اتفقنا؟
Why don't you tell me
لماذا لا تخبرني
what were you sneaking around for?
ما الذي كنت تتسلل من أجله؟
Anyway, I'm not going
على أي حال ، لن أذهب
to hang with such a deadbeat.
للتشبث بهذه الضربة القاضية.
It is hard to change one's nature.
من الصعب تغيير طبيعة المرء.
Then please, Mr. Mo,
ثم من فضلك ، السيد مو ،
leave quickly.
ترك بسرعة.
Don't let me get in your way.
لا تدعني أعترض طريقك.
I thought you changed
اعتقدت أنك تغيرت
when you came back this time.
عندما عدت هذه المرة.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
It is hard to change one's nature?
من الصعب تغيير طبيعة المرء؟
Come on!
هيا!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Cheers.
هتافات.
Liu,
ليو ،
you know what,
أتعلم،
Xia Xingrun
شيا Xingrun
has cast his covetous eyes
قد ألقى بعيونه الطمع
on the position of president
على منصب الرئيس
since Mr. Mu is not in the company.
لأن السيد مو ليس في الشركة.
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
you must help your aunt.
يجب أن تساعد عمتك.
Xia Xingrun
شيا Xingrun
is trying to win popular support.
تحاول كسب التأييد الشعبي.
The Mu Group
مجموعة Mu
is going to be Xia's.
سيكون شيا.
Only if you give your shares
فقط إذا أعطيت أسهمك
to your aunt
لعمتك
can she defeat Xia Xingrun.
هل يمكنها هزيمة شيا شينغ رون.
I won't do it!
لن أفعل ذلك!
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Huh?
هاه؟
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪